

OWEN MOOGK

RESPONSIBLE TECHNOLOGY ENTHUSIAST, WITH EXPERIENCE IN CUSTOMER SERVICE.

Address:

512 Little Dover Cres

Phone:

226-989-0602

Email:

owenmoogk@gmail.com

SKILLS

Have had plenty of experience in customer service, and always have a positive attitude towards situations.

Am proficient in Microsoft Office software, GSuite, and other basic computer programs.

Intermediate level front-end website development, using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Intermediate level industrial design using OnShape and Solidworks.

Novice graphical design and video editing skills.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Duke of Ed – Awarded Bronze and Silver Duke of Ed award for community service and involvement.

SHAD – I was accepted into a competitive month-long business and science program held at universities across the country.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BACKSHOP EMPLOYEE • MERRY HILL GOLF

2017 - 2020

- Have accumulated over 700 hours working as a Backshop employee at Merry Hill Golf Club.
- Learned many skills such as communication, responsibility, and cooperation.
- Gained many customer service experiences, learning skills transferrable to any workplace.

UMPIRE • WMBA

2020 - PRESENT

- Navigated difficult situations, employing management and cooperation skills.
- Promoted good sportsmanship and fun among young athletes.

SUB-TEAM LEAD • FIRST ROBOTICS

2018 - PRESENT

 Member of FIRST Robotics Team 2702, consisting of over 50 members. As a senior student, responsibilities include project management, cooperation, leadership, and teamwork.

EDUCATION

BLUEVALE COLLEGIATE INSTITUTE

2018 - 2022

- Completed 5 semesters with Honor Roll in all, and currently have an average of 95% through high school.
- Have been selected for Advanced Placement in both the Sciences and Mathematics.

COMMUNITY ACTIVITIES

DECA – International business competition, in which I advanced to the provincial championship in Toronto. It teaches quick thinking and business skills in a professional environment.

Choose to Lead — A four year leadership program run by Bluevale Collegiate, in which students develop leadership and management skills, as well as participate in activities giving back to the community